Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - O
        - One Way - Pop it; I'm in love with lovin' you, 1980; SR-21895; One Way; Hudson, Al (Box 379)
          In same jacket as # SR-21896. 2 copies. Promo
          Catalog # L33-1890; A-side Matrix # MCA 2348 W1
        - One Way - Pop it; I'm in love with lovin' you, 1980; SR-21896; One Way; Hudson, Al (Box 379)
          In same jacket as # SR-21895. 2 copies. Promo
        - One Way - Who's foolin' who, 1982; SR-21897; One Way (Box 379)
          Catalog # MCA-5279; A-side Matrix # MCA-2796-W2
        - One Way - Lady you are; Mr. Groove, 1984; SR-21898; One Way (Box 379)
          Catalog # L33-1173; A-side Matrix # MCA-3836-FDS-1
        - One Way - Let's talk, 1985; SR-21899; One Way (Box 379)
          Catalog # L33-1294; A-side Matrix # MCA-4488-FDS-2
        - One Way - Serving it, 1985; SR-21900; One Way (Box 379)
          Catalog # L33-17020; A-side Matrix # MCA-4618-FDS-1
        - One Way - You better quit, 1987; SR-21901; One Way (Box 379)
          Catalog # MCA-23716; A-side Matrix # MCA-6559-FDS-1
        - One Way - You better quit, 1986; SR-21902; One Way (Box 379)
          Catalog # L33-17269; A-side Matrix # MCA-6538-FDS-3
        - One Way - Don't think about it, 1986; SR-21903; One Way (Box 379)
          Catalog # MCA-23659; A-side Matrix # MCA 5814 FDS-9
        - One5Sex - Strip, 1998; SR-21904; One5Sex (Box 379)
          Catalog # PRO 4031-1; A-side Matrix # PRO-4031-1 A
          Fully Loaded Records
        - One5Sex - Strip, 1998; SR-21905; One5Sex (Box 379)
          Catalog # FL 4031-1; A-side Matrix # PRO-4031-1 A
        - O'Neal, Alexander - Hitmix (the official bootleg megamix), 1989; SR-21906; O'Neal, Alexander (Box 379)
          Catalog # 655504 6; A-side Matrix # 6555046 A1
          Tabu Records
        - O'Neal, Alexander - All mixed up, 1989; SR-21907; O'Neal, Alexander; Cherelle (Box 379)
          Catalog # Z 44492; A-side Matrix # PAL-44492-1A
        - O'Neal, Alexander - What's missing, 1985; SR-21908; O'Neal, Alexander (Box 379)
          Catalog # 4Z9 05361; A-side Matrix # 4Z9-05361-3AB
        - O'Neal, Alexander - Criticize, 1987; SR-21909; O'Neal, Alexander (Box 379)
          Catalog # 4Z9 07469; A-side Matrix # 4Z9-07469-3AA
        - O'Neal, Alexander - Hearsay, 1989; SR-21910; O'Neal, Alexander (Box 379)
          Catalog # 654667 6; A-side Matrix # 31 654667 20 1A1
        - O'Neal, Alexander - Aphrodisia (the remixes), 1993; SR-21911; O'Neal, Alexander (Box 379)
          Catalog # 31458 8192 1; A-side Matrix # 31458 8192 1A SP1
        - O'Neal, Alexander - Fake, 1987; SR-21912; O'Neal, Alexander (Box 379)
          Catalog # TBU 650859 6; A-side Matrix # 01-650859-1A-1
          Netherlands
        - O'Neal, Alexander - My gift to you, 1988; SR-21913; O'Neal, Alexander (Box 379)
          Catalog # Z 45016; A-side Matrix # PAL-45016-1B
        - O'Neal, Alexander - Dance hits of…., 2005; SR-21914; O'Neal, Alexander (Box 379)
          Catalog # HP-047; A-side Matrix # HP-047-A
          House Party
        - O'Neal, De De - Vulnerable, 1989; SR-21915; O'Neal, De De (Box 379)
          Catalog # 0-86253; A-side Matrix # STDM-57891-1
          Atlantic
        - O'Neal Shaquille - You can't stop the reign (album sampler), 1996; SR-21916; O'Neal Shaquille; Gunz, Peter; Jay-Z; Lord Tariq; Rakim; Biggie Smalls (Box 379)
          Catalog # INT8P 6064; A-side Matrix # INT8P-6064-A
        - O'Neal Shaquille - Make this a night to remember, 1998; SR-21917; O'Neal Shaquille; Gunz, Peter; Loon; Public Announcement; Sauce Money (Box 379)
          Catalog # TWPRO 00775; A-side Matrix # TWPRO 00775 A
          T.W.IsM. Records
        - O'Neal Shaquille - The way it's goin' down (TWIsM for life), 1998; SR-21918; O'Neal Shaquille; DJ Quik; Gunz, Peter (Box 379)
          Catalog # TWPRO 00732; A-side Matrix # TWPRO 00732 1 A
        - Only in the Dark - Make noise, 1988; SR-21919; Only in the Dark (Box 379)
          Catalog # PRO-7217; A-side Matrix # PRO-7217-A
          Profile Records
        - Ono, Yoko - Cape Clear; Walking on thin ice, 1985; SR-21920; Ono, Yoko (Box 379)
          Catalog # 883 872-1; A-side Matrix # 883-872-1-AS-ES
        - Ono, Yoko - Walking on thin ice, 1981; SR-21921; Ono, Yoko; Lennon, John (Box 379)
          Catalog # PRO-A-934; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-934-A1
        - Ono, Yoko - My man, 1982; SR-21922; Ono, Yoko (Box 379)
          Catalog # PRO 192; A-side Matrix # PRO-192-82-MP-6111-PRC-C1-1
        - Onyx - Last dayz, 1995; SR-21923; Onyx; P.I. (Box 379)
          Catalog # 314 577 115-1; A-side Matrix # 314-577-115-1-A
          JMJ
        - Onyx - React, 1998; SR-21924; Onyx; Big Pun; Noreaga (Box 379)
          Catalog # 314 568 983-1; A-side Matrix # 314568983-1-A
          Def Jam Recordings
        - Onyx - Throw ya gunz, 1992; SR-21925; Onyx; Mizell, Jason (Box 379)
          Catalog # 42 74766; A-side Matrix # XSS-74766-A-1A
        - Onyx - All we got iz us, 1995; SR-21926; Onyx; All City; P.I. (Box 379)
          Catalog # 314 529 265-1; A-side Matrix # 314-529-265-1-A
        - O.P.A. - Μητέρα Γη, 1992; SR-21927; O.P.A.; Χορωδία Περιστερίου (Box 379)
          Catalog # 7243 4 78730 1 0; A-side Matrix # YGOX 3347
          Minos
          Greece
        - Opal - Nice and slow, 1983; SR-21928; Opal (Box 379)
          Catalog # SC 14; A-side Matrix # SC 14-A
          Silver Cloud Records
        - Opgezwolle - Vloeistof (disc one), 2003; SR-21929; Opgezwolle; Blax; Ty (Box 379)
          In same jacket as # SR-21930. Double album.
          Catalog # TN 3003; A-side Matrix # 08 52834 20 1A1 TN 3003
          TopNotch
          Amsterdam, Netherlands
        - Opgezwolle - Vloeistof (disc two), 2003; SR-21930; Opgezwolle; Blax; Ty (Box 379)
          In same jacket as # SR-21929. Double album.
          Catalog # TN 3003; A-side Matrix # 08 52834 20 1V1 TN 3003
        - Optical - Cut throat flow; Lazy gun, 1996; SR-21931; Optical (Box 379)
          Catalog # MA 17; A-side Matrix # SMA 17 A
          Bear Necessities
        - Opus Seven - Bussle, 1979; SR-21932; Opus Seven (Box 379)
          Catalog # SOR-13944; A-side Matrix # MCA-1950
          Source Records
        - Orange Juice - Two hearts together; Hokoyo, 1982; SR-21933; Orange Juice (Box 379)
          Catalog # POSPT 470; A-side Matrix # POSPT-0000470-A
        - Oran Juice Jones - Player's call, 1997; SR-21934; Oran Juice Jones; Large, Stu (Box 379)
          Catalog # TB 422; A-side Matrix # TB 422 A
          Tommy Boy
        - Oran Juice Jones - Player's call, 1997; SR-21935; Oran Juice Jones; Large, Stu (Box 379)
        - Ørbit, William - Barber's adagio for strings, 1999; SR-21936; Ørbit, William (Box 379)
          Catalog # NR 20926; A-side Matrix # NR-20926-A-RE
          Maverick
        - Orbital - III, 1991; SR-21937; Orbital (Box 379)
          Catalog # FX 149; A-side Matrix # FX 149 A-1U-1-1
          FFRR
        - Orbiting Lula Remix Team - Dancing machine, 2003; SR-21938; Orbiting Lula Remix Team (Box 379)
          Catalog # SR-001; A-side Matrix # SR-001 A
          Spawn Records
        - Orchestra Harlow - Harlow's harem, 1972; SR-21939; Orchestra Harlow (Box 379)
          Catalog # SLP 00408; A-side Matrix # SLP-00408-A
          Fania Records
          Miami, Florida
        - Orchestral Manoeuvres in the Dark - Secret, 1988; SR-21940; Orchestral Manoeuvres in the Dark (Box 379)
          Catalog # SP-12272; A-side Matrix # A&M-SP-012272-A
        - Orchestral Manoeuvres in the Dark - Dreaming, 1988; SR-21941; Orchestral Manoeuvres in the Dark (Box 379)
          Catalog # SP-12258; A-side Matrix # A&M-SP-012258 A
        - Orchids - Life is a science, 1989; SR-21942; Orchids; Chica (Box 379)
          In same jacket as # SR-21943. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 13MF017; A-side Matrix # YGAS-81A1
          Major Force
          Tokyo, Japan
        - Orchids - Life is a science, 1989; SR-21943; Orchids; Chica (Box 379)
          In same jacket as # SR-21942. 2 copies.
        - Orchids - Yes, we can; I will call you; Go! Orchids, go!, 1988; SR-21944; Orchids (Box 379)
          Catalog # 15MF005; A-side Matrix # YGAS-68A1
        - Ordinary Folk - Brain EP, 1997; SR-21945; Ordinary Folk (Box 379)
          Catalog # FMD 006; A-side Matrix # FMD 006-A1
          Fragmented Records
        - Oregon - Impending bloom, 1983; SR-21946; Oregon (Box 380)
          Catalog # PRO-A-2095; A-side Matrix # 42026-A
          ECM Records
        - Orellana, Raul - The real wild house, 1989; SR-21947; Orellana, Raul (Box 380)
          Catalog # BCM 12322; A-side Matrix # 12322 A-1
          BCM Records
          Kaarst, Germany
        - Organic Tea - Simple music, 1994; SR-21948; Organic Tea (Box 380)
          Catalog # DOS OR DIE 015; A-side Matrix # DOS 015-A1
          Dos or Die Recordings
        - Organized Konfusion - Clean DJ sampler, 1997; SR-21949; Organized Konfusion (Box 380)
          Catalog # SPRO 30195; A-side Matrix # SPRO-30195 A
        - Organized Konfusion - Bring it on (The lost remix), 1996; SR-21950; Organized Konfusion; Ill Rahlos (Box 380)
          In same jacket as # SR-21951. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 30011; A-side Matrix # SPRO-30011-A
          Medicine Men Productions
        - Organized Konfusion - Bring it on (The lost remix), 1996; SR-21951; Organized Konfusion; Ill Rahlos (Box 380)
          In same jacket as # SR-21950. 2 copies.
        - Organized Konfusion - Clean DJ sampler, 1997; SR-21952; Organized Konfusion (Box 380)
          In same jacket as # SR-21953. Different discs. Promo
        - Organized Konfusion - Somehow, someway, 1997; SR-21953; Organized Konfusion (Box 380)
          In same jacket as # SR-21952. Different discs. Promo
          Catalog # SPRO 30167; A-side Matrix # SPRO-30167-A
        - Organiser - Bandit, 1989; SR-21954; Organiser (Box 380)
          Catalog # WR 1540; A-side Matrix # WR-1540-A
          Wrecker Records
        - Orgy - Opticon (disc one), 2001; SR-21955; Orgy (Box 380)
          In same jacket as # SR-21956. Double album. Promo
          Catalog # PRO-A-100531; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-100531-A/O-44976-A-SR1
          Reprise Records
        - Orgy - Opticon (disc two), 2001; SR-21956; Orgy (Box 380)
          In same jacket as # SR-21955. Double album. Promo
          Catalog # PRO-A-100531; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-100531-C/O-44976-C-SR1
        - Orient Express - A desert fantasy, 1978; SR-21957; Orient Express (Box 380)
          Catalog # 2424 192; A-side Matrix # 2424-192A-1Y
          Quebec, Canada
        - Origin Unknown - Sound in motion (disc one), 1998; SR-21958; Origin Unknown (Box 380)
          In same jacket as # SR-21959; SR-21960; SR-21961; SR-21962. quintuple album.
          Catalog # RAMMLP2; A-side Matrix # RAMMLP 2 A-1-1-1
          RAM Records
          Essex, United Kingdom
        - Origin Unknown - Sound in motion (disc two), 1998; SR-21959; Origin Unknown (Box 380)
          In same jacket as # SR-21958; SR-21960; SR-21961; SR-21962. quintuple album.
          Catalog # RAMMLP2; A-side Matrix # RAMMLP 2 C-1-1-1
        - Origin Unknown - Sound in motion (disc three), 1998; SR-21960; Origin Unknown (Box 380)
          In same jacket as # SR-21958; SR-21959; SR-21961; SR-21962. quintuple album.
          Catalog # RAMMLP2; A-side Matrix # RAMMLP 2 E-2-1-1
        - Origin Unknown - Sound in motion (disc four), 1998; SR-21961; Origin Unknown (Box 380)
          In same jacket as # SR-21958; SR-21959; SR-21960; SR-21962. quintuple album.
          Catalog # RAMMLP2; A-side Matrix # RAMMLP 2 G-02-1-
        - Origin Unknown - Sound in motion (disc five), 1998; SR-21962; Origin Unknown (Box 380)
          In same jacket as # SR-21958; SR-21959; SR-21960; SR-21961. quintuple album.
          Catalog # RAMMLP2; A-side Matrix # RAMMLP 2 I-1-1-1
        - Original - Hey Mr. M.C., 1997; SR-21963; Original; Born Predators; Infinite (Box 380)
          Catalog # 5010-1; A-side Matrix # 5010-1A
          World Won Records
          Deal, New Jersey
        - Original Swing Machine - It don't mean a thing (if it ain't got that swing), 1986; SR-21964; Original Swing Machine (Box 380)
          Catalog # 5941-1-RDAB; A-side Matrix # 5941-1-RD-A-1
        - Orion - Deep inside, 2000; SR-21965; Orion (Box 380)
          Test Pressing; Promo
          Catalog # RISE 087; A-side Matrix # RISE 087 A
          Rise
        - Orlando, Tony - They're playing our song, 1979; SR-21966; Orlando, Tony (Box 380)
          In same jacket as # SR-21967. 2 copies. Promo
          Catalog # NBD 20152 DJ; A-side Matrix # NBD-20152-AS-RE-1
          Casablanca
        - Orlando, Tony - They're playing our song, 1979; SR-21967; Orlando, Tony (Box 380)
          In same jacket as # SR-21966. 2 copies. Promo
        - Orlando, Tony - Don't let go, 1978; SR-21968; Orlando, Tony (Box 380)
          Annotated. Promo
          Catalog # AS-11390; A-side Matrix # AS S 11390 ASP-1A
        - Orphan Family - Freak train, 1997; SR-21969; Orphan Family (Box 380)
          In same jacket as # SR-21970. 2 copies.
          Catalog # LFR-0036; A-side Matrix # LFR-0036-A-RE-1
          Low Frequency Recordings
          New Jersey
        - Orphan Family - Freak train, 1997; SR-21970; Orphan Family (Box 380)
          In same jacket as # SR-21969. 2 copies.
        - Orphans - Love song; Shades of grey, 1995; SR-21971; Orphans (Box 380)
          Catalog # KIDS009; A-side Matrix # KIDS-009-A
          Kids Records
          Bayonne, New Jersey
        - Orquesta de la Luz - Salsa caliente del Japon (hot salsa from Japan / 日本からの熱いサルサ), 1990; SR-21972; Orquesta de la Luz (Box 380)
          Catalog # RML-80420; A-side Matrix # RM-80420 A-GIB
          RMM Records
        - Orquesta Costa Brava - De costa a costa, 1983; SR-21973; Orquesta Costa Brava (Box 380)
          Catalog # TTH-1858; A-side Matrix # CB 1001 A
          Top Ten Hits
        - Orquesta la Selecta de Raphy Leavitt - Payaso, SR-21974; Orquesta la Selecta de Raphy Leavitt (Box 380)
          Reissue
          Catalog # DG-1212; A-side Matrix # DG-1212-A
          Borinquen
          San Juan, Puerto Rico
        - Ortiz, Joell - Brooklyn, 2002; SR-21975; Ortiz, Joell; Noriega from Afrique (Box 380)
          Catalog # GP001; A-side Matrix # OKU-015-A
          Townz Soundz
        - Orup - Orup, 1988; SR-21976; Orup; Wistrand, Karin (Box 380)
          In same jacket as # SR-21977. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 242 264-1; A-side Matrix # 242264-1-A2
          WEA
          Sweden
        - Orup - Orup, 1988; SR-21977; Orup; Wistrand, Karin (Box 380)
          In same jacket as # SR-21976. 2 copies.
        - Os Batuqueiros e as Mulatas - Mete bronca batuqueiro (operação samba), 1972; SR-21978; Os Batuqueiros e as Mulatas; Goulard, Mirian; Rodrigues, Pedrinho (Box 380)
          Catalog # 107.0130; A-side Matrix # 107.0130-A
          RCA Camden
          Brazil
        - Os Míopes - Rap rock, 1995; SR-21979; Os Míopes (Box 380)
          No Discogs entry with this Catalog # for LP
          Catalog # 443.007; A-side Matrix # 443 007 A
          Afegan
          Rio de Janeiro, Brazil
        - Os Míopes - Rap rock, 1995; SR-21980; Os Míopes (Box 380)
          Annotated. No Discogs entry with this Catalog # for LP.
          Catalog # 443.008; A-side Matrix # 443 008 A
        - Os Míopes - Rap rock, 1995; SR-21981; Os Míopes (Box 380)
          Catalog # 443.010; A-side Matrix # 443 010 A
        - Os Míopes - Rap rock, 1995; SR-21982; Os Míopes (Box 380)
          Catalog # 443.011; A-side Matrix # 443 011 A
        - Os Míopes - Rap rock, 1995; SR-21983; Os Míopes (Box 380)
          Catalog # 443.009; A-side Matrix # 443 009 A
        - Os Reis do Batuque - Batucada N° 4, 1977; SR-21984; Os Reis do Batuque (Box 380)
          Different jacket
          Catalog # 6349 318; A-side Matrix # AC 200 6349 318 A1
          Philips
        - Osborne & Giles - Stranger in the night, 1985; SR-21985; Osborne & Giles (Box 380)
          Catalog # SPRO70050; A-side Matrix # V-1-70050-A
          Red Label
        - Osborne, Jeffrey - Plane love, 1983; SR-21986; Osborne, Jeffrey (Box 380)
          Catalog # SP-12089; A-side Matrix # A+M-SP-012089-A-ES1
        - Osborne, Jeffrey - Soweto, 1986; SR-21987; Osborne, Jeffrey (Box 380)
          Catalog # SP-12190; A-side Matrix # A+M-SP-012190-A-ES-1
        - Osborne, Jeffrey - I really don't need no light, 1982; SR-21988; Osborne, Jeffrey (Box 380)
          Catalog # SP-17194; A-side Matrix # A&M SP 017194 A-T2
        - Osbourne, Johnny - Reasons; Dead man tell no tail, 1994; SR-21989; Osbourne, Johnny; Chilla Rinch (Box 380)
          Catalog # MB-44; A-side Matrix # MB-044-A
          Massive B
        - Osbourne, Johnny - Reasons; Dead man tell no tail, 1994; SR-21990; Osbourne, Johnny; Chilla Rinch (Box 380)
          In same jacket as # SR-21991. 2 copies.
        - Osbourne, Johnny - Reasons; Dead man tell no tail, 1994; SR-21991; Osbourne, Johnny; Chilla Rinch (Box 380)
          In same jacket as # SR-21990. 2 copies.
        - Osbourne, Johnny - Budy bye, 1995; SR-21992; Osbourne, Johnny (Box 380)
          Catalog # SPRO 50867; A-side Matrix # 53177-A
        - Osbourne, Johnny - Budy bye, 1995; SR-21993; Osbourne, Johnny (Box 380)
        - Osbourne, Johnny - Sweet mouth, 1988; SR-21994; Osbourne, Johnny; Lady G (Box 380)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # GUSSIE-8902-A
          Anchor Record
          Kingston, Jamaica
        - Oscar - Mental ability to be different, 2000; SR-21995; Oscar (Box 380)
          Catalog # CF2842; A-side Matrix # CF-2842-A
          Caffeine Records
          Massapequa Park, New York
        - Osé - Party beat, 1984; SR-21996; Osé (Box 380)
          In same jacket as # SR-21997. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 1957; A-side Matrix # TR-1957-A
          Treasure
          North Miami Beach, Florida
        - Osé - Party beat, 1984; SR-21997; Osé (Box 380)
          In same jacket as # SR-21996. 2 copies.
        - Osibisa - Osibisa, 1971; SR-21998; Osibisa (Box 380)
          Catalog # DL 75285; A-side Matrix # LNMG7 236E5
          Decca
        - Osibisa - Black magic night (disc one), 1977; SR-21999; Osibisa (Box 380)
          In same jacket as # SR-22000. Double album.
          Catalog # BRON 505; A-side Matrix # BRON 505 A-2
          Bronze
        - Osibisa - Black magic night (disc two), 1977; SR-22000; Osibisa (Box 380)
          In same jacket as # SR-21999. Double album.
          Catalog # BRON 505; A-side Matrix # BRON 506 A-2
        - Osibisa - Celebration, 1980; SR-22001; Osibisa (Box 381)
          Catalog # CEL 6707; A-side Matrix # CEL 6707 A
          Celluloid
          Paris, France
        - Osibisa - Black magic night (disc one), 1977; SR-22002; Osibisa (Box 381)
          In same jacket as # SR-22003. Double album.
          Catalog # ARBOL 3; A-side Matrix # ARBOL 3-1
        - Osibisa - Black magic night (disc two), 1977; SR-22003; Osibisa (Box 381)
          In same jacket as # SR-22002. Double album.
          Catalog # ARBOL 3; A-side Matrix # ARBOL 3/3
        - Osiris - Osiris the band!, 1980; SR-22004; Osiris (Box 381)
          Catalog # TD-0005; A-side Matrix # TD 5A-1A
          Tom Dog Records
          Washington, D.C.
        - Oskar, Lee - Haunted house, 1978; SR-22005; Oskar, Lee (Box 381)
          Catalog # AS-11398; A-side Matrix # ASS 11398ASP
        - Osmonds - The plan, 1973; SR-22006; Osmonds (Box 381)
          Catalog # SE 4902; A-side Matrix # SE 4092 MGS 3178 1
          MGM Records
        - Osmonds - I,I,I; You're mine, 1979; SR-22007; Osmonds (Box 381)
          Catalog # MK-91; A-side Matrix # MK-91-A1
        - Alone again e outros sucessos de Gilbert O'Sullivan - Gilbert O'Sullivan, 1986; SR-22008; Alone again e outros sucessos de Gilbert O'Sullivan (Box 381)
          No Discogs entry
          Catalog # 90.001; A-side Matrix # FAMA 90.001 A
          Fama
        - Otierre - Dalla sede (disc one), 1997; SR-22009; Otierre; La Pina; Rivalcapone; Sole Bee; Toni L. (Box 381)
          In same jacket as # SR-22010. Double album.
          Catalog # 537 436-1; A-side Matrix # 537905 1 1 520
        - Otierre - Dalla sede (disc two), 1997; SR-22010; Otierre; La Pina; Rivalcapone; Sole Bee; Toni L. (Box 381)
          In same jacket as # SR-22009. Double album.
          Catalog # 537 436-1; A-side Matrix # 537906 1 1 520
        - Our Boys Steel Orchestra - Pan night and day, 1988; SR-22011; Our Boys Steel Orchestra (Box 381)
          Catalog # MLPS 9822; A-side Matrix # MLPS-9822-A
          Mango
        - Our Daughter's Wedding - Digital cowboy, 1981; SR-22012; Our Daughter's Wedding (Box 381)
          Catalog # MLP-19000; A-side Matrix # MLP-1-19000-Z-5
          EMI America
        - Our Daughter's Wedding - Elevate her, 1982; SR-22013; Our Daughter's Wedding (Box 381)
          Catalog # SPRO-9819; A-side Matrix # SPRO-1-9819-Z1
        - Out of Hear - Family affair, 1986; SR-22014; Out of Hear (Box 381)
          Catalog # V 1206; A-side Matrix # V-1206 A
          Vuocolo Records
          East Point, Georgia
        - Outbar - Away from the heat, 1984; SR-22015; Outbar (Box 381)
          Catalog # 12EMI 5581; A-side Matrix # 12EMI 5581 A-1U-1
          EMI
        - Outcast - Rollercoaster, 1996; SR-22016; Outcast (Box 381)
          Catalog # 107TP12; A-side Matrix # 107TP12P A-1
          One Little Indian
        - Outhere Brothers - Boom boom boom, 1995; SR-22017; Outhere Brothers (Box 381)
          Catalog # AU-1100-1; A-side Matrix # AU-1100-1-A
          Aureus Records
          Mashpee, Massachusetts
        - Outhere Brothers - Boom boom boom, 1995; SR-22018; Outhere Brothers (Box 381)
        - Outkast - Ain't no thang; Crumblin' erb; Hootie hoo, 1994; SR-22019; Outkast (Box 381)
          Catalog # LFDP-4084; A-side Matrix # LFDP-4084-SA
          LaFace Records
          Atlanta, Georgia
        - Outkast - Ain't no thang; Crumblin' erb; Hootie hoo, 1994; SR-22020; Outkast (Box 381)
        - Outkast - So fresh, so clean, 2001; SR-22021; Outkast (Box 381)
          Catalog # LFDP-4529; A-side Matrix # LFDP-4529-SA
        - Outkast - Jazzy belle, 1996; SR-22022; Outkast (Box 381)
          Catalog # LFDP-4225; A-side Matrix # LFDP-4225-SA
        - Outkast - Skew it one the bar-b, 1998; SR-22023; Outkast; Raekwon (Box 381)
          Catalog # LFDP-4351; A-side Matrix # LFDP-4351-SA
        - Outkast - ATLiens (instrumental version) (disc one), 1996; SR-22024; Outkast (Box 381)
          In same jacket as # SR-22025. Double album. Promo
          Catalog # LFLP-6033; A-side Matrix # LFLP-6033-SA SP1
        - Outkast - ATLiens (instrumental version) (disc two), 1996; SR-22025; Outkast (Box 381)
          In same jacket as # SR-22024. Double album. Promo
          Catalog # LFLP-6033; A-side Matrix # LFLP-6033-SC SP1
        - Outkast - ATLiens (clean version) (disc one), 1996; SR-22026; Outkast (Box 381)
          In same jacket as # SR-22027. Double album. Promo
          Catalog # LFLP-6032; A-side Matrix # LFLP-6032-SA-SP1
        - Outkast - ATLiens (clean version) (disc two), 1996; SR-22027; Outkast (Box 381)
          In same jacket as # SR-22026. Double album. Promo
          Catalog # LFLP-6032; A-side Matrix # LFLP-6032-SC-SP1
        - Outkast - Player's ball, 1993; SR-22028; Outkast (Box 381)
          Catalog # 73008-24061-1; A-side Matrix # 73008-2-4061-1-SA
        - Outkast - Elevators (me & you), 1996; SR-22029; Outkast (Box 381)
          Catalog # LFDP-4187; A-side Matrix # LFDP-4187-1A
        - Outkast - Southernplayalisticadillacmuzik, 1994; SR-22030; Outkast (Box 381)
          Catalog # LFDP-4070; A-side Matrix # LFDP-4070-SA1